So I'm doing seven million this year.
If I add nothing else to my business
and we are getting almost all my leads
from speaking at events.
But the problem is is that right now
my growth is capped by my schedule.
I hit the same like industry events
for the past couple of years
and they're starting to dry out a little bit.
You would probably be really well served
learning to run a webinar.
So I would take your best performing content
as your first 20 ads that I would start with.
And then just film like a five second, by the way,
like I'm doing a webinar on this thing.
I just spoke at this, this, this,
and people had to pay to be there.
I'll give it to you for free to show up
that actually has real value.
And I would say like, I would probably pitch
some sort of like savings assessment for free,
which is like, if you just show us your growth rate
in your current payroll,
we'll show you what you could be saving.
It would be dropping to your bottom line with increases.
Like this isn't just swap what you have
for someone for less.
This is get someone who's better for less
and who can work some of your leads.
Like, you know what I mean?
It's like, no one wants to get sold just for less.
It's like, this is better than what you have
and costs less.
So I would probably even my first like 20 to 40 ads.
And I would also put a banner across the top
that says occupational therapist, physical therapist,
speech therapist, so that they know like it's for them.
And then it's literally a simple opt-in page.
You send them a Zoom link with reminders.
That's it.